“跟杜威摇滚”继续保持在第二位
And it's Rockin' With Dewey continuing to race in second.
NETFLIX 出品
接着是“马歇哈尔”和“最后一刻”“完美同盟”…
Then comes Masherhal, Hand Over Bell and Perfect Alliance
NETFLIX 原创电影
…仍然位居后列 用时56.6秒
is still at the back of the field in 56 and 3/5 seconds.
现在“MF偶然” 在拐角处冲到领先位置
And now MF Happenstance leads the charge around the far turn.
“MF偶然”领先四分之三个马身位
MF Happenstance, three quarters of a length.
“神秘女人”在外道占据第二
Mystery Woman second on the outside,
“跟杜威一起摇滚”在内道位列第三
Rockin' With Dewey is third to the inside.
后面依次是“最后一刻” “马歇哈尔”
And they're being followed by Hand Over Bell, Masherhal,
“完美同盟”仍被甩在后面
and Perfect Alliance is still at the back.
它们开始冲刺了 1.21公里 用时 84.2 秒
And they're into the stretch, three quarters in 1:24.2.
仍然是“MF偶然”领先
And it is still MF Happenstance,
外道的“神秘女人”奋起直追
and here comes Mystery Woman to the outside.
-到中间“最后一刻”… -不
-And in the center, Hand Over Bell... -No.
加油
Come on.
现在第一的是“神秘女人”“最后一刻”远在外道
It is Mystery Woman, Hand Over Bell on the far outside.
-“马歇哈尔”在最后关头… -加油 马歇哈尔
-Masherhal is closing late... -Come on, Mashy.
最先冲过终点线的是最后一刻
Here at the finish it's Hand Over Bell!
-我赢了 -马歇哈尔是第二
Yeah, I got it. -Masherhal was next,
第三是“跟杜威一起摇滚”
then came Rockin' With Dewey
“神秘女人”用时 111.4 秒
and Mystery Woman in 1:51.4 .
7块 还是5块？
Seven. Or five for us?
应该他告诉你
On should tell you.
好 拜拜
Okay. Bye.
圣母玛利亚
Matko Boska.
5块？
Five?
什么？
What is it?
我们5块
Five, for us.
11块
Eleven.
我要开始吃了
I'm starting.
不 我们等他一起
No, we wait for him.
喂？
Hello?
你有一通 来自大西洋郡监狱的付费电话
You have a collect call from the Atlantic County Correctional Facility
-呼叫人是… -达伦
-from... Darren.
如果接受请按“1”
Press one to accept.
-达伦 -喂
-Darren. -Hey.
-你在哪里？ -监狱
-Where are you? -Jail.
天啊 你干了什么？
Jesus. What did you do?
没事 我一直想给你打电话
No, it's nothing. I've been trying to call you.
你的手机没交费吗？
You didn't pay your fuckin' cell phone?
我周一才拿薪水 怎么回事？
Yeah, I get paid on Monday. What happened?
-我在大西洋城 -妈妈
-I'm down in Atlantic City. -Ma.
我砸了一个混蛋的窗户
Just some asshole, I ended up having to smash in his window.
轻罪 重点是我得在这里过夜
Misdemeanor. Point is, I'm stuck here. I gotta spend the night.
所以我才需要你帮我 明天我有件事要办
Which is why I need you to help me out. I got this thing going on here tomorrow...
你得假装是我 替我去办
so you gotta do it and pretend you're me.
你要上一个人的车去送一个手提箱
You'll get in a guy's car and deliver a briefcase.
什么都不用担心
Don't worry about anything.
办好我能赚1500块 你知道我需要这笔钱
There's $1,500 in it for me. You know I need it.
好吗？我会非常为你骄傲
All right? I'll be very proud of you.
-箱里有什么？ -就是个手提箱
-What's in the suitcase? -It's a briefcase.
里面到底有什么？
What's in the briefcase?
我不知道
I don't know.
不 我才不…你不知道吗？
No, I'm not doing-- You don't know?
只是文件而已
It's just papers, man.
没什么大不了的
It's nothing major.
我不干
I'm not doing that.
-让妈妈接电话 -不
-Put Ma on the phone. -No.
丹尼
Danny!
让妈妈接电话
-Put Ma on the phone.
小姐 我已经告诉过你了
Miss, I already told you,
如果没有票 那你得下车
if you don't have a ticket you'll have to get off the train.
丹尼尔
Daniel...
你哥哥需要你 你要去做
Your brother needs you. You're doing it.
（麦塔成站）
你听好
Okay, look, just listen, all right?
会有个女人拿一个绿包坐在长椅上
There'll be a woman on a bench with a green purse.
你拿你的包和她的互换
And you swap your briefcase for hers.
-绿包 -你不会要写下来吧？
Green purse. -You're not writing this down, are you?
没有
No.
好 别犯傻 我真的需要这笔钱
Good. Don't be stupid, I really need this money.
我欠你一次
I owe you one, all right?
我会帮你交话费
I'll pay your cell phone bill.
好吗？她有个绿包…
All right? She's got a green pocketbook and--
好 但是谁开车？
All right, but whose-- whose car am I getting into?
-什么？ -快点
-What? -Wrap it up.
稍等一下 你必须帮我 好吗？
Just one sec. You just got to do this for me, okay?
我会帮你 但是谁开车？
I'm gonna do it. Who's the guy driving the car?
答应我你会帮我 丹尼 答应我你会…
Promise me you'll do this. Danny? Promise me you'll do--
我帮你 但是谁开车？
I'm doing it, but who's the guy driving the car?
能刷一下卡吗…
You got a swipe? You got a swipe?
有个人 应该是费城来的
[man] There's this one guy, like, from Philly, I think.
他们一看就像费城人
They got like a Philly vibe, and, uh...
拉塞尔和吉米认识他
Russell and Jimmy know him.
拉塞尔一直很让人蛋疼 但吉米明白
Russell's been a big pain in the ass, but Jimmy gets it, you know?
他知道我能帮他
Like, he knows I can come through for him.
那次被抓后事情就很奇怪 但这次情况不错
Shit's been weird since the bust, but this is a good situation
因为这伙人是专业的
'cause these guys, they're professional.
不像豪威那个混蛋 根本不知道自己在做什么
Not like Howie, that fuck. That guy doesn't know what he's doing.
而且计划很周密 明白我的意思吗？
And the plan is intricate, you know what I mean?
就跟表一样
It's like a clock, you know.
一切都完美契合在一起 所有人都很安全
Everything fits together and everyone gets protected.
我想要更多钱
I want more money.
-不行 -我开车
-No. -I'm driving.
我让表正常运转
I'm keeping the clock running.
你在说什么？是你来找我要活干
What are you talking about? You came to me for work.
你到底是怎么丢了那份工作的？
I mean, how'd you lose that job anyway?
创作理念差异
Creative differences.
真的吗？
Really?
瑞克的支票兑换骗局呢？
And how's, uh, Ricky's check cashing con paying off for you?
可没人让你为了一个油腔滑调的混蛋
Because no one asked you to skip town to Pittsburgh
大老远跑去匹兹堡
for some greaseball shithead.
他让我去了
Yeah, well, he did.
我是说 如果你不回匹兹堡
I mean, if you don't go back to Pittsburgh,
我有张大号双人床
I have a... queen size bed.
你做过更不堪的
You've done worse.
我要回匹兹堡 所以我睡沙发就行 斯科特
Well, I'm going back to Pittsburgh, so I'm fine on the couch, Scott.
把活儿做好就行
Just do the job.
这是手机 不要往外打电话
This is the phone. Don't make any outgoing calls.
这是森特拉的钥匙
And these are the keys to the Sentra.
-你不是说是阿蒂玛吗？ -是辆破尼桑 无所谓了
-Thought you said it was an Altima. -It's a fuckin' Nissan. Doesn't matter.
整条街就这一辆红色尼桑
It's, like, uh, gonna be the only red Nissan on the block.
-手提箱里有什么？ -我不知道
-What's in the briefcase? -I don't know.
你不能什么都知道 艾莉
You can't know everything, Ellie.
有时候你只要做事就行了
Sometimes you gotta just do it.
（拿骚大道站）
好了
Here you go.
费莉西亚 我可以走吗？
Felicia, I can go?
是你吗？
Are you the guy?
是
Uh... yeah.
Yeah.
是你吗？
You the guy?
是我 没错
Yeah, I'm the girl.
好
Right.
我知道了
I can see that.
上车
Get in.
你知道那个人长什么样吗？
Do you know what the-- the-- the guy looks like?
不知道
No.
是个男的 对吧？
It is a guy, right?
不要熄火
Keep the car on.
把后车窗玻璃摇下来
Roll this back window down.
他回来了…
He's coming back, he's coming back.
-你说他们看到车牌了吗？ -我不知道
-Do you think they got the license plate? -I don't know.
因为…
Because, man...
你知道跟我碰面的 拿绿包的女孩是谁吗？
Do you know who the girl is I gotta meet with the green bag?
-祝你好运 -好的
-Good luck. -All right.
（阿斯托利亚大道车站）
拜托
Come on, man.
搞定了
Yeah, it's done.
天啊 是你
Oh, my God-- Oh, my God, it's you.
你不知道我刚才做了什么
You don't even know what I just did.
站住 你去哪里？
Look, stop. Where are you goin'?
听我说 不要跑…求你了
Look-- Don't run, don't run, don't run, please don't run.
我只是需要一个号码之类的 我只是需…
I just need a number or something, I just need...
我不知道 一个地址之类的
I don't know, an address or something, like...
你不帮我吗？
You're not gonna help me?
我刚把手提箱给错人了
I just gave the briefcase to the wrong woman.
没错 我们该怎么办？
Exactly. What are we gonna do?
我该怎么办？我不该在这里的
What am I gonna do? I'm not supposed to be here.
我根本不该在这里 是我哥哥的事
I'm not even supposed to be here, it's my brother.
-你知道我哥哥达伦吗？ -别告诉我他的名字
-Do you know my brother Darren? -Don't fucking tell me his name.
你为什么不想知道？
Why don't you wanna know?
听我说…这样你也拿不到 你的1500 知道吗？
Look, look! Look, you're not gonna get your 1,500 either, okay?
-1500？ -对 1500 我就知道这么多
-1,500? -Yeah, 1,500. That's all I know.
-我只知道绿色… -他们给你1500美元？
-All I know is the green-- -They're paying you fuckin' $1,500?
应该是吧 我不知道
I think so. I don't even know.
把你的手机给我…快给我
Give me your phone. Give me your fucking phone.
我没有…我没交话费
I don't have a-- I didn't pay my bill.
我们怎么办？
What are we gonna do?
你有硬币吗？
You got a quarter?
我有电话卡 你要给他打电话吗？
I got a phone card. You gonna call him?
你要给他打电话吗？
You're calling him?
-该死 -这又不是造火箭
-Fuck. -This is not fucking rocket science.
能有多难？你走去站台
How hard is it? You walk up to the fucking platform,
-把箱子换了 -我知道
-you exchange the suitcase. -I know.
八岁小孩子都能做好
I got an eight-year-old that can do it.
你把事交给该死的波拉克 看看发生了什么
You give it to this fuckin' Pollack, look what happens.
-你真是太蠢了 -别说了 拉塞尔
-You're so fucking stupid-- -Stop talking, Russell!
闭嘴
-Stop talking! -[cell phone ringing]
等一下 哪位？
Hold up. Who's this?
-你好 -我们出问题了 对吧？
-Well, hello there. -[man] I think we got a problem.
当然了 1500块？斯科特
Yeah, no shit. $1,500, Scott?
为什么一个白痴拿的钱是我的两倍？
Why is some idiot getting twice as much as me?
-他现在跟你在一起吗？ -是的
-He with you now? -Yes.
东西在你那里吗？
Do you have the thing?
不在
No.
但我知道它接下来会去哪儿
But I have the address where it's going.
我们应该能搞定 但是需要点时间
I think we got it under control, okay? Just gonna take a little longer.
没事 我们能搞定
It's fine. We got it under control.
你要出钱
It's gonna cost you.
好 1500整给你
Okay. The full $1,500.
两倍
Twice that.
我不关心 从你的那份里出
What the fuck do I care? It's comin' out of your share.
-好 -我们也需要见达伦
-Okay. -We need to see Darren, too.
她要带达伦来 这件事办好前我不想让他到处跑
And she brings Darren. I don't want him running around until this is done.
好 你今晚把东西和达伦都带来
Okay, so you deliver the thing and you bring him with you tonight.
他的那份也给你
You can keep his share, too.
好 没问题
Okay. All right.
新埃博尼宾馆 1310室 晚10点
New Ebony Hotel, Room 1310, 10:00 p.m.
1310室 知道了 我们走
1310, got it. Let's go.
等一下…你不需要我了 你知道地址了
Wait, wait, you don't need me. You-- You got the address.
包给你吧 我不要了
Take the bag, I don't want it anymore.
那个女人长什么样？
What does the woman look like?
她是金发 穿了一件白衬衣
She's got blonde hair, she had a white shirt on.
-她… -所以才叫上你 我们走吧
-She's... -Yeah, exactly. Let's go.
（中央火车站）
药瓶上的地址是什么来着？
[Ellie] What's the address on the pills again?
玛丽艾斯路31号
31 Maryasis Road.
在布瑞尔克利夫
It's in Briarcliff.
哪列车到布瑞尔克利夫？
[Ellie] Hi, what train goes to Briarcliff?
奥西宁或斯卡布罗 哪列离你近坐哪列
Ossining or Scarborough, whichever one is closer to you.
-斯卡布罗 -12点20发车 40号轨
-Scarborough. -12:20, track 40.
好的 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
你要猜猜我的名字吗？
You want to guess what my name is?
我叫丹尼
My name is Danny.
-告诉我你的名字吧 -我才不告诉你
-Come on, tell me your name. -[scoffs] I'm not telling you my name.
好吧 你是哪里人？
All right. Where are you from?
听着 是你搞砸了 所以你什么都无权知道 明白吗？
Look, you fucked up, so you lost "knowing shit" privileges, all right?
-知道吗？你真的是个… -什么？
-You know, you can be a real-- -A what? Huh?
-贱人吗？ -什么？
-A real bitch? -What?
不…
No, no.
我本来想说你真难捉摸的 但…
I was-- I was gonna say you can be a tough nut to crack, but...
你真的打算说我难以捉摸吗？
Were you really gonna say "a tough nut to crack"?
是 怎么了？这么说怎么了？
Yeah. Why, what's wrong with that?
我住在匹兹堡
I live in Pittsburgh.
匹兹堡怎么样？
How's Pittsburgh?
很多烂人
A lot of shitty people.
很遗憾
Oh. I'm sorry.
别这样 又不是你建的
Don't be sorry. You didn't build it.
你在匹兹堡跟谁一起住吗？
So, you live with anyone in Pittsburgh?
你有没有室友或者男朋友？
You know, you got a roommate or, you know, you got a boyfriend?
我跟一个瑞奇一起住
I live with a Ricky.
一个瑞奇是什么？
What's a Ricky?
我以前养过一条蜥蜴 就叫瑞奇
I had a lizard named Ricky once.
听起来很合适
Sounds about right.
走吧 等办好了就行了
Come on, you'll be done when it's done.
（奥西宁村）
你觉得谁会住在这里？
Who do you think lives out here?
有钱人
Rich people.
你觉得这里的房子要多少钱？
So, how much do you think these houses cost?
-怎么？你要买房子吗？ -不是
-Why? You in the market? -Oh, no.
萨克拉门托呢？你去过吗？
What about, uh, Sacramento? You ever been there?
没有 谢天谢地
No, thank God.
那里有个工作机会
There's a job opening there.
因为我是个厨师
'Cause I'm a chef, you know?
在城里一个很不错的餐馆里
At a nice restaurant in the city.
你知道“农场到餐桌”吧？
You know what "farm to table" is, right?
其实我更像个厨子
I'm more of a cook, I guess.
知道了 随便 但你不用离开纽约
Okay, sure, whatever, but you don't have to leave New York.
我知道 但…
Yeah, I know, but...
我的生活条件并不好
my living situation's not great.
好吧 但到处都有餐馆
Fine, but there's restaurants everywhere.
这倒没错
That's true.
你呢？你是做什么的？
So what about you? What do you do?
-我最近没工作 -真的吗？
-I'm recently unemployed. -Oh, really?
你以前做什么的？
What did you do?
我之前是个酒保
I-- I was a bartender.
但我会做很棒的鸡尾酒
But I made-- I made, like, fancy cocktails.
不错 我有个朋友勒夫 我们是高中同学
That's cool. I got this friend Lev that I went to high school with,
他是市里一家酒吧的 调酒师助理 他…
he-- he's a bar-back in the city at this bar and he's just like...
他最喜欢调的酒是蛋白…
His favorite drink to make is, like, these egg whites--
行了 我没做过酒保 我在脱衣舞俱乐部工作过
Look, I wasn't a bartender, okay? I worked in a strip club.
好吧…
All right. Okay.
你肯定做得很成功
I bet you were successful at that, you know.
-这话什么意思？ -没什么 只是…
-What the fuck's that supposed to mean? -Nothing, just 'cause--
你又漂亮又聪明 还…
You're pretty and you're smart, and...
我不成功
Well, I wasn't.
我只是个服务员 我不跳脱衣舞或在后面工作
And I was only a waitress, okay? I didn't strip or work the back.
-好吧 -我是认真的 我不陪睡
-All right. -I'm serious. I don't sleep around.
-你不信我吗？ -我信
-What, you don't believe me? -I believe you.
-你猜我跟多少人睡过 -这不重要
-Guess how many guys I've slept with. -It doesn't matter--
-不 你猜猜看 -我不猜 这太傻了
-No, no. Guess. -I'm not guessing, that's stupid.
-我不会猜的 -七个
-I'm not gonna guess. -Seven.
-好吧 -不多
-Okay. -It's not a lot.
不多 我可能还会说得更多
It's not a lot. I probably would've said higher.
你现在想说我看着像妓女吗？
Oh, so you're saying I look like a whore now?
不是 我…
No! I just...
我…即使你跟一百个人睡过
I just-- I wouldn't even think you were a whore
我都不会觉得你是妓女
if you slept with, like, a hundred guys.
说得没错
Yeah, exactly.
-你算老几？还评判我 -我没有评判你
-Who are you to judge me? -I'm not judging you.
所以我才不想猜
That's why I don't wanna guess.
我们迷路了
We're lost.
-不应该 -我之前见过那栋房子
-Uh, we shouldn't be. -No, I've seen that house before.
不一定 说不定你小时候来过这里
I don't know. Maybe you were here when you were a kid.
如果刚才左拐对了 那这就是玛丽艾斯路
You know, if that was the right left, then this is Maryasis.
如果他们树个路标 我们就能知道了
If they put up a fuckin' street sign we'd be able to tell.
-你干什么？ -找地址看看
-Hey, what are you doing? -Looking for an address.
不…你不能这样 这是联邦犯罪
No, no, you can't do this, it's a federal crime.
好吧 反正我有同伙
Yeah, well, I got an accomplice.
就是这条街
Look, it is the right street.
快放回去
Put it away.
需要帮忙吗？
Can I help you?
-你好 你住这里吗？ -不
-Hey. Um, do you live here? -I do not.
-我们也是 -不
-Neither do we. -No.
你们看起来不像库蒂考夫家的人
You don't look much like the Kutikoffs.
库蒂考夫  是  我们应该…
The Kutiko-- Yeah, uh-- We're supposed to just, you know...
-他们…我们… -我们迷路了
-They're-- We're just... -We're just a little lost.
-我们迷路了 -没错
-We're just a little lost. -That's it.
知道我迷路时怎么做吗？
You know what I do when I'm lost?
我会报警 要我帮你们报警吗？
I call the police. Shall I call them for you?
-不用 -不用 谢谢 我们要走了
-No, no. -No, thanks. We're just gonna leave.
-谢谢 -好主意
-Thank you. -[man] Good idea.
抱歉
Sorry.
没事 他开的是越野
Don't worry about it. He's driving a fucking SUV.
-什么意思？ -他是个混蛋
-What does that mean? -He's an asshole.
家里好像没人
I don't think anyone's home.
在客厅里 不要让狗跑出来
Hey. It's in the living room. Don't let the dog out.
Uh...
-是她拿走了那个包吗？ -不是 这个更年轻
-Is that the girl that took the bag? -No, no. This girl is younger.
看看吧
Uh, I guess.
我觉得她说的不是我们的箱子
I don't think she's talking about the briefcase.
我们得找她问问
I think we just have to find her and ask her.
对 我们去找她
Yeah. Yeah, let's do that.
有人吗？
Hello?
快看 是个瑞奇
Hey, look, it's a Ricky.
天啊 快看
Oh, my God, check it out.
这条蜥蜴真大
That's a big lizard.
我不懂他们为什么给孩子 活不久的宠物
I don't know why they give kids pets that die so young.
可能想让他们在遇到真正伤心的事前 先小小地伤心一下
Maybe let 'em be sad about something small before the really sad things happen.
来吧
Come on.
而且蜥蜴的寿命很长的
And, you know, lizards have a really long lifespan.
有20年
Like, 20 years.
那瑞奇怎么了？
So what happened to Ricky?
它的生活条件也不太好
Uh, well, his living situation wasn't exactly ideal either.
谁的好？
-Ya know. -Whose is?
这些人的好
These guys'.
-对 -有人吗？
-Yeah. -[Danny] Hello.
有人吗？
Hello?
[Ellie] Hello?
-她去哪里了？ -对 狗在哪里？
-Where is she? -Yeah, and where's the dog?
快看 有人回家了
Hey, look, someone's coming home.
我觉得那是…开越野的那个人
I think that-- That's the guy with the SUV.
什么？
What?
藏起来 快
Hide. Hide.
你干什么？快走
What are you doing? Come on.
-得跳下去 -什么？
-[whispers] We gotta jump. -What?
我们得跳下去
[whispers] We gotta jump.
没问题的
[softly] We got this, okay?
该死
Fuck.
来吧 快跳
[mouthing] Come on. Jump!
快点
Come on.
我们没把狗放出来
We didn't let the dog out.
这样吧 我再回去一趟
You know what? Look, I'm going back up there.
我要回去一趟
I'm going back up there.
我要跟他们解释 你拿着我的身份证
I'm going to explain to them. Take my ID.
如果我被捕 我要告诉他们一个假名
If I get arrested I'm gonna give a false name.
名字不是问题 他们家一半的人见过你
The name isn't the problem, you've been seen by half the family.
我们等到他们早上出门吧
Let's just wait till they go in the morning.
女主人可能把箱子放在里面了 我们进去拿了走
The wife will probably leave the briefcase inside, we'll go in and get it.
-如果不在呢？ -那我们就走 好吗？
-And what if it's not there? -Then we'll leave, all right?
我们等到明天看看
We just got to wait and see.
对不起 是我搞砸了
Look, I'm sorry, all right? I screwed up.
是我的错 我放弃我的那份 好吗？
It's my fault. I'm gonna forfeit my share, okay?
-但我不能整晚留在这里 -你必须留下
-But I can't stay here the whole night. -No, you have to.
为什么？说真的 你应该跟我一起走
Why? Why? And honestly, you should come with me.
我们应该让他们来处理
We should let them deal with this.
这是他们的问题 这跟我们无关
This is-- This is their problem. This has nothing to do with us.
除非你知道 一个破产的人怎么赚到足够的钱
Unless you know how someone who's broke can make enough money
摆脱自己的糟糕处境 否则我就留下
to get out of a shitty situation, then it's worth it to me.
你要用赚的钱离开那个人吗？
Are you using the money to get away from that guy?
是的 行了吗？
Yes, okay?
我要用这笔钱离开匹兹堡
I'm using the money to leave Pittsburgh.
好
Okay.
对了
Hey, uh...
刚才你做得很好
good job back there.
没有把狗放出来什么的
You know, from not letting the dog out and stuff.
（汽车旅馆）
-你要点东西吗？ -当然
-You gonna order something? -Yeah, sure.
9块钱能点什么？
Um, what can we get for nine dollars?
包括小费吗？
Is that including tip?
是的
Sure.
能借用一下你的手机吗？
Can I use your phone?
-这里是语音信箱 机主是… -斯科特
-You have reached the voice mailbox of... -Scott.
请在滴声后留言
-Please leave a message after the tone.
是我
Hey, it's me.
我们没事 正在办 但耽搁了
We're fine, we're on it but we got delayed.
所以等明天才能办好
So it won't be going down till tomorrow.
对 我们早上会去汽车旅馆
So, yeah, we'll be at the motel in the morning.
-他怎么说？ -他没接电话
-[Danny] So what'd he say? -Couldn't reach him.
好 我们吃点东西吧
All right, look, let's get some food.
你想吃吗？我想 我快饿死了
You need food? I need food, I'm starving.
-好吗？ -好
-Yeah? -All right, yeah.
儿童餐还是开胃菜？
Kids' menu or appetizers?
你呢？你有室友或女朋友吗？
So what about you? You got a roommate, girlfriend?
去年我跟我们楼一个女孩约会过
Well, I was-- I was seeing this girl in my building last year.
真的吗？嘴唇上 带着你的小胡子和她约会吗？
Oh, really? With that little hair thing above your lip?
我的小胡子怎么了？
What's wrong with my mustache?
好吧 还有谁？
All right, who else?
-我不想跟你说这个 -拜托 和我说说吧
I don't wanna talk about this with you. -Come on, give me something.
达伦情况很糟？
Very bad for Darren?
妈妈 我的情况也可能很糟
Ma, it could be very bad for me.
高中呢？
What about high school?
走廊勾搭小女生？楼道里动手动脚？
Some scandalous hallway hookups? Some stairway action?
好吧
All right.
丽贝卡瓦加斯 她在十年级时碰了我的鸡鸡
Rebecca Vargas. She touched my penis in tenth grade.
-丽贝卡瓦加斯？ -对 丽贝卡瓦加斯
-Wow. Rebecca Vargas? -Yeah, Rebecca Vargas.
当时丽贝卡瓦加斯…天啊
Rebecca Vargas back then... Oh, my God, man.
不过我不知道算不算
Ohh. I don't know if it counts, though.
-为什么不算？ -这…
-Why wouldn't it count? -Well...
好吧 我一个朋友迈克布达宾
All right. Mike Budabin, a friend of mine,
他告诉大家 谁先让丽贝卡瓦加斯
he told everyone that whoever got Rebecca Vargas
碰了自己的鸡鸡 谁就赢得“特别奖”
to touch their penis first, wins the "Special Prize."
什么特别奖？
What was the Special Prize?
就是让丽贝卡瓦加斯碰你的鸡鸡
It was having Rebecca Vargas touch your penis.
-有道理 -对
-Makes sense. -Right.
总之 她知道了奖跟自己有关
Anyway, she found out about this prize being associated with her
所以想知道到底是什么
and she wanted to know what it was.
所以她问了我 我说会告诉她 但是…
And so she asked me, and I said that I would tell her, but...
她必须先碰我的鸡鸡
she had to touch my penis first.
所以她用小指轻轻碰了
So she tapped it with her pinky and...
所以我就赢到了特别奖
that's how I won the Special Prize.
（趣味游戏）
丹尼尔 快点回家
Daniel, just come home now.
你要做晚餐 赌马的人明天一大早就来
You'll make supper, and the bettors are coming early tomorrow.
我们应该让达伦处理的
We should just let Darren handle it.
对
Yeah.
丹尼尔？
Daniel?
我要留下过夜
I'm gonna stay.
丹尼尔…喂？
Daniel? Daniel? Hello?
谢谢
Thank you.
我不知道这是我听过的最甜蜜的故事
I don't know if that's the sweetest or saddest story
还是最悲伤的故事
I've ever heard in my life.
不 是最甜蜜的…
No, no, no, it's the sweetest. It's the sweetest.
说明一下 算数的
For the record, it counts.
-真的吗？ -当然了
-Really? -Yeah, of course.
她都碰你的鸡鸡了 对吧？
I mean, she touched your penis, right?
（缤纷滑梯）
（打星星）
（嘉年华）
你不觉得我们该睡在林子里吗？
You don't think that we should just sleep in the woods?
我才不睡林子里
I am not sleeping in the woods.
-如果有警报呢？ -泳池边的小屋吗？
-What if this is alarmed? -The pool shed?
-我不知道 -不用担心 没有警报
-I don't know. -Don't worry. It's not alarmed.
来吧 享受生活
Just come on. Live a little.
所以他最后上了法庭
So he ends up going to court
他在法庭上说:“那是鬼魂”
and he was in the courtroom going "It was a ghost."
法官就说:“我知道那鬼魂 我见过”
And the judge is like, "I know the ghost. I've seen it."
他就被无罪释放了
So he got off.
Whoa.
话说你都烹饪什么？
So, what do you cook?
什么都烹饪
Everything.
我是说在餐馆里
-I mean, at the restaurant. -Oh. Um...
那是个很不错的意大利餐馆
It's, uh, it's a nice little Italian place.
你去过吗？意大利？
You ever been there? To Italy?
没有…
No. No.
我只去过普罗维登斯
I mean, the only place I've ever been is Providence.
你就应该去那里
Well, that's where you should go.
忘记萨克拉门托吧
Forget Sacramento.
好
Yeah.
我去过一次
I've been there once.
-是吗？ -去过意大利
-[Danny] You have? -To Italy, yeah.
你跟家人还是谁一起去的吗？
Wow. Did you go with your family or something?
不是
No.
-抱歉 我不… -没事
-I'm sorry, I didn't... -Don't be sorry.
你喜欢那里吗？
Do you like it there?
应该吧
Yeah, I guess.
当你不把自己当游客 你会发现意大利有很多不可靠的人
Italy has a lot of shady people once you get past all the tourist stuff.
这样
Right.
你没想过 可能不是那个地方不可靠
You don't ever think that maybe it's-- it's not the place that's shady,
而是你选择打交道的人不可靠吗？
it's the people you're choosing to hang out with.
你不如周末先去个 普罗维登斯之外的地方
You know, why don't you go somewhere else besides Providence for the weekend
然后再表现出一副无所不知的样子
before you start acting like you know everything.
-抱歉 -不…没事
-I'm sorry. -No, it's-- No, no, it's okay.
我就是太冷了
I'm just cold.
如果你冷 我们可以抱在一起
You know, if-- if you are cold, we could-- we could hold each other.
什么？
Excuse me?
我们可以抱在一起取暖
You know, we could hold each other for warmth.
你想抱我吗？
You wanna cuddle me?
这是天气学事实 我不是想…
Look, it's a meteorical fact. I'm not, you know.
是气象学
Meteorological.
我就是这个意思
That's what I meant.
如果你不老实 我发誓你一定会后悔
If you try anything, I swear to God you're gonna fuckin' regret it.
不会 我有点怕你 所以我不会…
No, I'm-- I'm a little scared of you, so I'm not...
好
Okay.
好吗？
Yeah?
我们只是抱在一起取暖
We're only cuddling for warmth.
对 因为天气原因抱在一起
Yeah. Cuddling for weather purposes.
是我 我们没事 正在办 但耽搁了
Hey, it's me. We're fine. We're on it, but we got delayed.
所以等明天才能办好
So it won't be going down till tomorrow.
我们早上会去汽车旅馆
So, yeah. We'll be at the motel in the morning.
是艾莉的留言 一切都好
So that was Ellie. And it's fine, you know.
他们有点耽搁了 但是明早会去 所以…
Uh, they're a little delayed, but they'll be there in the morning, so...
你送我去汽车旅馆就行 一切安好
Just drop me off at the motel and it's all good.
这哪里是一切安好了？
What exactly is good about that?
这…她能搞定
It's, uh-- You know, she has it.
-她说的吗？ -对
-She said that? -[Scott] Yeah.
把留言给我听听
Let me hear the message.
我删除了
I deleted it.
她会去的 她需要那笔钱
She'll be there. I mean, she needs the money.
她也会带上他 否则她拿不到他那份 所以…
I mean-- and she's gotta bring him too, or else she won't get his share, so...
一切都会顺利办好
You know, it'll work out.
-就跟在卡姆登一样吗？ -那都是三年前的事了 吉米
-Like it worked out in Camden? -That was three years ago, Jimmy.
别提了好吗？
Come on, man. [stammers]
往前看
Move on.
对 对你我来说 往前看或许是个好主意
Yeah, maybe for you and me moving on is a good idea.
我不是那个意思
-That-- That's not what I mean.
是达伦
It's Darren.
达伦 你在哪里？
Darren, where are you, man?
伙计 我迟了点 现在在我妈妈家
Hey, man, I'm-- I'm running a little late. I'm at my mom's house.
在你妈妈家是什么意思？
What do you mean you're at your mom's house?
我有事耽搁了 我马上去汽车旅馆
I, uh, got a little delayed. I'll be at-- I'll be at the motel soon.
那跟艾莉在一起的是谁？
Well, then, who the fuck is with Ellie?
他们出来了
[Ellie] All right, here they come.
显然她在家里地位最高
Whoa. She's clearly running the family.
对 他好像没了她就会迷路
Yeah, he looks like he'd be lost without her.
你知道他迷路时会怎么做
And you know what he does when he's lost.
报警…
Calls the police.
好了 希望她把箱子留在里面了
All right, hopefully she left the briefcase inside.
不…拿绿包的人不是她
Oh, no, no, no, no. That's not the woman with the green bag.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
那个人大概年轻30岁
She was like, I don't know, 30 years younger.
-你确定吗？ -确定
-Are you sure? -Yeah.
该死
Shit.
-如果她把门锁了呢？ -你刚才看到她没锁了
-[Danny] What if she locked it? -You just saw her not lock the door.
住在这地方 就是为了
The whole point of living out here
不用担心我们这样的人
is so they don't have to worry about people like us.
好吧…
All right, all right.
-看 -拿着
-Hey! -Take it.
-这是她吗？ -对 是她
-Hey, is this her? -Yeah, that's her.
-我猜这是女儿 -但药在她包里
-I guess it's the daughter. -But she had the pills.
不清楚 药肯定是她妈妈的
I don't know, they must be her mom's.
走
Come on.
家里有电脑 找到了 好
There's a computer. Boom. All right.
我把他们的姓氏输进邮箱
So, I just put their last name into their email
应该会出现一些信息
and-- and something should come up.
等等 怎么拼？
Wait, how do I spell it?
-韦… -林…韦林格 出来了
- W-E-I-R-E-- - I-R... Wierengo. I got it.
好了
All right.
有戴维韦林格、艾瑞克韦林格
We got Dave Wierengo, we got Eric Wierengo.
维尼莎韦林格 是“尼”
Vinessa Wierengo, with an "I" in the Vinessa.
-哪里？ -维后面
- Where? - After the "V."
“妈 你记得那家宾馆的名字吗？”
"Hey, Mom, do you remember the name of the hotel?"
找到了
Blah-blah-blah, blah-blah-blah... All right!
-什么？ -找到了
-What? -We got it.
“维尼莎韦林格 市场协调员 安娜贝拉顾问 西30街242号”
"Vinessa Wierengo, Marketing Coordinator. Annabella Advisors, 242 West 30th Street."
-天啊 -太棒了
-Oh, my God! -Yes! All right!
好 我去换衣服
All right, I'm-- I'm gonna go change.
什么？换衣服是什么意思？
Why, what? What do you mean change?
因为我觉得身上很脏
Because I feel fuckin' filthy.
你去找点吃的
Just go grab some food.
-好… -好吗？
-All right. Yeah. -Okay?
行动
Let's do it!
你在里面吗？我们该走了
Hey, you in there? We should probably get out of here.
好 稍等一下
Yeah. Just a minute.
穿上这个
[Ellie] Hey. Put this on.
好
Sure.
我们走吧
Come on. Let's go.
你觉得如何？
So, what do you think?
什么？
About what?
我的小胡子
About my mustache.
不知道 好像还是有胡子好看
Yeah, I don't know. Maybe you looked better with it.
你看起来很棒
You look great.
至少比之前好
At least better than whatever was going on there before.
你们楼里所有女孩子肯定会喜欢
And I'm sure all the girls in your building will love it.
我不想要我楼里的女孩子
I don't want the girls in my building.
（米兰酒吧）
（宾馆）
（热狗）
（星期六下午禁止停车）
（洗衣店）
（《新闻时报》）
（烤面包、玉米饼、龙舌兰）
我妈妈在吗？
Is my mom there?
或者你能让我哥哥接电话吗？
Or can you put my brother on?
他们没事 你把地址告诉我就行
They're fine. Just give me the address.
维尼莎韦林格 安娜贝拉顾问
Vinessa Wierengo, Annabella Advisors.
-西30街242号 -西30街242号 知道了
-242 West 30th Street. -242 West 30th Street. Got it.
维尼莎的维后面是尼
And that's-- that's with an "I" after the "V" in Vinessa.
后面不是常见的娜
It's not Vanessa.
-你们等着 -好
Just sit tight. -Okay.
我会派人去 如果她走 你们跟着她
I'll send guys over. If she leaves, stay with her.
她想知道钱的事
She wants to know about the money.
钱呢？
What about the money?
她会拿到我们说好的数目
She'll get what we agreed to.
我要你去找他们 在汽车旅馆外跟斯科特见面
I want you to go to them, then meet Scott outside the motel.
达伦 我和艾莉说好的是
Oh, and Darren, what me and Ellie agreed to...
她要拿走你那份
she's taking your share.
我得去大便
I gotta take a shit.
对 安娜贝拉顾问 西30街242号
Uh, yeah, Annabella Advisors. Uh, 242 West 30th Street.
你好 安娜贝拉顾问
Hello. Annabella Advisors.
能帮我找一下维尼莎韦棱格吗？
Could you connect me with, uh, Vinessa Winergo, please?
好的 是韦林格 请稍等
-Uh, yes. Wierengo. Please hold.
你好 我是维尼莎
Hello, this is Vinessa.
韦林格小姐 你好
Ms. Wierengo. Hi. Yeah. Um...
你可能有个手提箱本是属于我的
I believe you may have a briefcase that belongs to me.
天啊 是的
Oh. Oh, my God, yes.
就在我办公室里 我的包在你那里吗？
I-- I'm-- I have it right here in my office. Do you have my bag?
你的包？是在我这里
Your bag? Yeah, I've got it.
是这么回事 我马上要参加一个重要会议
Here's the thing, I'm about to walk into a very important meeting right now
手提箱里有重要文件 我马上就需要
and there are some essential documents in it that I need right now.
我…
Oh, well, I...
今天天气这么好 出办公室走走如何？
Look, it's a beautiful day outside. Why not get out of the office, right?
不行 达伦
No fucking way, Darren.
我不管多久 你不能出去干活
I don't care how long it takes, you're not running any errands.
喂？
Hello?
先生 我们看到箱子了
Sir, uh, we got the briefcase.
-真的吗？ -是的…
-Really? -Yeah, yeah.
-怎么看到的？ -我不知道
-How? -I-- I don't know.
她出大楼了 手里拿着那个手提箱
She walked out of her building and she had the briefcase with her.
所以我们决定跟着她
So we decided to follow her, right?
好 但我只让你们盯着她
All right, but I told you to just stay on her.
是…
Uh, yeah, yeah.
但我们觉得…
But then we started thinking like...
你觉得她要去哪里？
Where do you think she's going with it?
不知道 你觉得她会去找警察吗？
I don't know. Do you think she's gonna go to the cops?
我不知道
I don't know.
-这样有道理 -对吧？
-Yeah, that makes sense, I guess. -Right?
所以我们决定紧紧盯着她
So we decided to keep, uh, real close and-- and-- and watch her,
我们一刻也没让她离开过视线
and we didn't take our eyes off her one bit.
她起来了
[Ellie] She's getting up.
我们得拿到那个手提箱
We gotta get that briefcase.
我穿着她妈妈的裙子
I'm wearing her mom's dress.
好吧 我去拿
All right. Let me deal with it, all right?
-等一下 你好 -你好
-Hey. Hey! Hi. -Oh, hey.
抱歉 我不知道你是不是记得我 但你的包在我这里
Sorry, I don't know if you remember me but I got your bag.
我当然记得 你好
Yeah, yeah, of course. Hi.
我真的很抱歉 我不小心拿错了 不是…
I'm really sorry, I just took it by mistake. It wasn't like--
没事…我知道 没事 给你
No, no, I know. Don't worry. I got it. Here.
好…
Right. Right.
-谢谢 -谢谢 太谢谢你了
-Thanks. -Thank you! Thank you so much.
那我先走了 但是谢谢你
I guess I'm gonna head back down here, but thank you.
-祝你会议顺利 -谢谢
-Good luck with your meeting. -Thank you.
-她就那么…给我了 -我们走
She just gave-- She just gave it-- -Let's go!
我什么都没跟她说
I didn't even say anything to her.
我们做得特别聪明 她一点都没起疑
We were real smart about it, too, like she didn't suspect a thing at all.
好 我不需要听全部细节
All right. I don't need to hear the whole story.
到汽车旅馆外跟我见面
Just meet outside the motel.
好的 先生 我能跟我哥哥说话吗？
Okay. Um, sir, can I talk to my brother, please?
他们想在汽车旅馆外跟我们见面
They want us to meet at the motel.
-他们拿到手提箱了 -什么？
-They got the briefcase. -What?
看来你小子走运
Looks like you're a lucky son of a bitch.
-达伦？ -是我
-Darren? -Yeah.
我们拿到手提箱了 我们成功了
We got the briefcase, man. We came through.
你还跟那个女孩在一起吗？说波兰语
Are you there with the girl? Talk in Polish.
是的
Yeah.
谢天谢地
Thank fucking God.
听着 她在耍我们
Listen, she's screwing us over.
什么？不 她没有
What? No, she's not.
她跟他们谈好了 她会拿到我那份
She cut a deal with them. She gets my share...
只要她看着你把事情办好
if she babysits you until it's done.
不…她其实挺好的
No, no. She's really cool.
听着 丹尼 我知道你可能喜欢她
Listen, Danny, I know you probably like her and all,
但你想想
but think about it.
她肯定一直紧紧跟着你 对吧？
I bet she was real insistent on you sticking around the whole time, right?
你觉得她为什么那样？
Why do you think she would do that?
你还在听吗？
You there, kid?
在
Yeah.
听我说 我很抱歉 丹尼
Look, I'm sorry, Danny.
她是个大骗子 脱衣舞女
She's a con artist. Stripper.
是服务员
Waitress.
随便
Yeah, whatever, man.
重点是你就是她的支票
Point is, you're a fucking paycheck to her.
但如果你把手提箱带回来
But if you bring the briefcase back,
那我就能拿到全部酬劳 让她白忙活了
then I can get the whole share and cut her out of it.
丹尼？
Danny?
你把手提箱带回家
Just get the briefcase and come home.
好吗？
All right?
好
Yeah.
你会说俄语？
You speak Russian?
波兰语
Polish.
然后我想到我们中场休息时溜进去
Then I figured out we were-- we were sneaking in at intermission.
不过我有点喜欢那样
I don't know, I kind of preferred it that way, though.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
没事
Nothing.
怎么了？
What?
-快告诉我怎么了 -我被炒了 好吗？
-Come on, tell me what's up. -I got fired, all right?
他们给我妈妈打了电话
They called my mom.
达伦刚告诉我 没事的
Darren just told me. It doesn't matter.
很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我没去上班 这样正常
I missed my shift, it happens.
无所谓
It doesn't matter.
等等…听我说
Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Listen.
我在想 等我们去汽车旅馆
I was thinking that when we get to the motel...
你应该在附近等着
you should just wait nearby.
好吗？让我一个人 去交手提箱 我能行
All right? Let me go up there alone and handle it. I got it.
我要给我的经理打电话
Look, I'm gonna call my manager, all right?
我想听听她怎么说 我不想…
Okay? I just wanna see what she's saying. I don't wanna...
你稍等一下 好吗？
Just give me a minute?
好…没问题
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Sure.
小姐 你有公车卡吗？
[man] Miss, you got a Metro card?
没有 我拿了我的包就走
No. I just gotta get my bag.
（纽约州驾驶证）
-丹尼 -妈妈
-Danny. -Hey, Mom.
你没有拿…
You didn't bring the--
你没有拿手提箱回来？
You didn't bring the fucking briefcase?
你开玩笑吗？丹尼
Are you fucking kidding me, Danny?
你开玩笑吗？
[punching his palm] Are you fucking kidding me?
-你觉得很好玩吗？ -对
-It's fucking funny to you, man? -Yeah.
斯科特
Scott.
艾莉
[Scott] Ellie.
-我给你打电话了 我… -我知道…
-Hey! I tried to call you. I tried to-- -Yeah, yeah.
快上去
Yeah, yeah.
Hey.
Hey. Hey.
那个女孩…
That girl...
她不会离开任何人
She isn't gonna leave anybody.
即使她以为她会
Even if she thinks she is.
她也不会
She isn't.
相信我
Trust me.
你说什么？
What did you say? Huh?
-你跟我说什么？ -去死
-What are you saying to me? -Fuck you.
我说的就是这个
That's what I'm saying.
-拉塞尔 我们去哪里？ -我不知道 去见一个富婆
-Russell, where are we going? -I don't know. To some rich lady.
妈妈 别管 你别管好吗？别管
Ma! Leave it. Just leave it, okay? Leave it.
对不起…
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
妈妈
Ma.
进来
[woman] Come in.
进来 你可以把东西放下
Come in. You can-- You can put that down.
放那里
Right there.
很好
Very good.
坐吧
Sit.
你知道密码是多少吗？
You wanna know the combination?
三个零
Zero-zero-zero.
这是这些人做的 唯一一件不过分复杂的事
It's about the only thing these guys did that wasn't Byzantine in its complexity.
但你也知道有些男人是什么样
But you know how some men are.
他们以为他们让东西越复杂 这东西就越吸引人
They think the more intricate they make something, the more impressive it is.
就是这个
Ah, there you are.
律师说我拿不到的唯一一件东西
The one thing the lawyer said I couldn't get.
我拿到了
And I got it.
我想告诉你件事
I want to tell you something:
绝不要嫁给一个不爱自己母亲的男人
Never marry a man who doesn't love his mother.
信封里有3000块
There's $3,000 in that envelope.
谢谢
Thank you.
你可以走了
You can-- You can leave.
我会让吉米知道事情办好了 其他人都能拿到钱
And I'll let Jimmy know it's done so everyone else can get paid.
好
Okay.
我们去哪里？
[Russell] So where we going?
今天我们不开张
Not today. We're not open.
我们只是…我们要…
-We're just-- We're gonna--
你是谁？
[Ola] Who are you?
我是…
I'm, uh...
-我是丽贝卡瓦加斯 -丽贝卡瓦加斯？
-I'm Rebecca Vargas. -[mother] Rebecca Vargas?
是吗？
-Yeah? -[mother speaking in Polish]
对 我们是高中同学 妈妈 你不记得了吗？
Yeah, we went to high school together, Ma. You don't remember?
Hey.
1400、1500
$1400, $1500.
别都在俱乐部花掉了
Don't spend it all at the club.
拿着吧 别给你哥哥
Take it. And don't give it to your brother.
你要去哪里？
So where are you gonna go?
坐车去匹兹堡
Bus to Pittsburgh.
是吗？
Yeah?
你不是说你要离开那里吗？
I thought you said you were gonna leave there.
是的
I am.
我只是…
I just...
我…
-I... -[scoffs]
-我欠他的 -好
-I owe it to him. -Yeah.
好
Right.
等等
Just wait.
你没有…
You know, you know, you don't...
你需要一张公交卡
You need a Metro card.
我可以买一张
I-- I think I can buy one.
不行 因为你只有百元钞票
You can't because you only have hundreds
那些机器都不好用了 我想给你
and those machines are crappy and-- and I wanna give you...
我的公交卡
my Metro card.
谢谢
Thanks.
…二、三、四、五
...two, three, four, five.
妈妈…
Ma, Ma.
先生 我给你100块买你的卡
Sir, sir, I'll give you $100-- 100 for your card.
我怎么知道这不是假钞？
Whoa. How do I know that's not counterfeit?
不是
It's not.
帮我刷一下…
Give me a swipe, give me a swipe.
刷一下…
-One swipe. -One swipe.
谢谢
Thanks.
你好 去匹兹堡的下一班车 是什么时候？
Hi. When's the next bus to Pittsburgh?
下午6点40分 票价57块
Uh... 6:40 p.m. The ticket is $57.
-小姐？ -算了
-[woman] Miss? -Yeah, uh-- never mind, actually.
下一班去普罗维登斯的车 是什么时候？
When's the next bus to Providence?
（港务局汽车站）
抱歉…
Sorry! Sorry, sorry! Sorry.
Hey! Hey!
我没想到你…
I-- I didn't think you...
听我说…
Look. Look.
我也想去 我就一路跑来了
I was gonna go and I-- and I just-- I just ran all the way here.
怎么了？
What's going on?
听我说
Look...
我想跟你一起去匹兹堡
I want to go to Pittsburgh with you.
我不去匹兹堡
I'm not going to Pittsburgh.
那你去哪里？
Well, where you going?
普罗维登斯
Providence.
是吗？
Yeah?
我能跟你一起去吗？
Can I come with you?
当然可以
Yeah. Sure.
是吗？
Yeah?
-是 -是吗？
-Yeah. -Yeah?
等等
Wait.
-对不起 我不该… -没事
-I'm sorry, okay? I shouldn't have-- -It's okay.
不…我不该那么做
-It's okay. -No, no, I shouldn't have done that.
我不该那么做 对不起 我…
I shouldn't have done that. I'm sorry, I just...
-我道歉 好吗？ -不用…道歉
-Look, I apologize, okay? -Don't be. Don't-- Don't be sorry.
我只是不…
I just didn't...
该死
Oh, shit.
你还想去吗？
Do you still wanna come?
想
Yeah.
我还想去
Yeah, I still wanna come.
那就好
Okay, good.
关于那个吻…
And about the kiss...
不是我…
it's not that I...
我只是不…
I just don't...
那是个开始
It's a start.
-好吗？ -好
-Okay? -Yeah.
好…
-Yeah. -Yeah.
好 那对我是开始
Yeah. I'll take a start.
对我也是
Yeah, me too.